<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="desc_about"><![CDATA[
<h1>Introduction</h1>
<p>Why another one? Just to have:</p>
<ul>
    <li>Local pty, USB UART etc. support in the same application;</li>
    <li>Adequate screen input methods as long as a terminal requires specific keyboard
    functions.</li>
</ul>
<h1>Features and bugs</h1>
<ul>
<li>Interface for custom connection modules in separate applications will be added later.</li>
<li>Supported USB UART devices: Generic USB CDC, CP210X, FTDI, PL2303, CH34x, CP2130 SPI-USB.</li>
<li>No SSH in the Lite version.</li>
<li>And no MoSH.</li>
<li>Telnet (no encryption).</li>
<li>Local Linux pty is supported. Feel free to follow directions from
<a href="http://kevinboone.net/android_nonroot.html">
<i>Using standard Linux utilities in a stock, non-rooted Android device</i>
by Kevin Boone</a>. ;)</li>
<li>The introduction of a shell utility to interact with the Android environment has been started.
Content exchange between other applications and own files / pipes has been implemented
like in Termux. USB serial port dongle access from the command line has also been implemented
(unlike Termux) ;).</li>
<li>Arbitrary content providers support will be added later.</li>
<li>Different charsets and customizable key mapping support.</li>
<li>Builtin screen keyboard and mouse.</li>
<li>Minimum supported Android version is 4.0 Ice Cream Sandwich.</li>
</ul>
<p>Please, be aware, that key mapping of hardware input devices is provided by device vendors
and it could make some troubles.
For example: ASUS ZenFone 4 Max has the hardware keyboard `Home\' (KEYCODE_MOVE_HOME) key
mapped as the Android middle (KEYCODE_HOME) button that makes it effectively invisible for
applications.
Most vendors also maps mouse right and middle buttons in some unexpected ways.
Fortunately, mouse buttons mapping can usually be worked around.
Most usual right mouse button mapping as the Android `Back\' (KEYCODE_BACK) button
is supported by this application.
The only way to change the vendor\'s mapping is to root your device and change appropriate files
manually.</p>
<p>Due to an USB bug in Android itself, it\'s highly recommended not to use the USB UART
with devices running Android 5.1.1 Lollipop.
See <a href="https://github.com/felHR85/UsbSerial/issues/142">this issue</a> for more details.</p>
<h1>Credits</h1>
<p>Thanks to:</p>
<ul>
    <li><a href="https://github.com/felHR85">felHR85</a> and other contributors for
    <a href="https://github.com/felHR85/UsbSerial">UsbSerial</a> library
    (<a href="https://github.com/felHR85/UsbSerial/blob/master/LICENSE">license</a>);</li>
    <li>Creators of
    <a href="https://www.fontsquirrel.com/fonts/dejavu-sans-mono">DejaVu Sans Mono</a> font
    (<a href="https://www.fontsquirrel.com/license/dejavu-sans-mono">license</a>).</li>
</ul>
<h1>Source</h1>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://github.com/green-green-avk/AnotherTermLite">GitHub</a></li>
</ul>
]]></string>
</resources>
